youthconnectmag.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Youth Connect

**Updated: September 20, 2013**

At Youth Connect, we take privacy of the information you share with us very seriously. We respect the personal nature of the information that you provide to us on our website www.youthconnectmag.com or any of its subsidiary sites hosted on www.youthconnectmag.com or www.yc-m.in or any of the sub-domains of these primary domains. This policy document governs the use of your information by us or our partners, associates or subsidiaries. This privacy policy document may be changed wholly or to a part, at any time, and we encourage you to check this document often to ensure that you are familiar with our Privacy Policy.

Your use of Youth Connect website or any of its subsidiary sites indicates that you have read and understood this privacy policy document and you agree to adhere to the Terms of Service document that is practice.

### **Information We Collect**

**Collection of your personal information:** You may provide personal information to Youth Connect at several points on the website that includes (1) sharing your e-mail address while subscribing for our newsletters (2) submitting your personal information while sending us an email to any official email address associated with Youth Connect, (3) sharing your personal information while filing up for a position here at Youth Connect using the team application form, (4) sharing your personal information while sending us feedback or contacting us for any purpose, (5) sharing your personal information for filing up any other form on the Youth Connect website or any of its subsidiary sites, (6) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories, (7) by sharing contact information for participating in our contests, (8) by participating in a survey where an email address is requested.

Every time you provide us contact information of yours, you give Youth Connect right to use that information to contact you for the purpose you provided the information for. Unless you give us your consent, no other party than Youth Connect will contact you for any matter whatsoever. However, in certain exceptional cases, we may have to disclose personally identifiable information of yours. These cases may include (i) directions of court(s) of law or any government agency, (ii) requirements of any law enforcement agency, (iii) or in situation where we merge or are acquired by a different entity.

In any case, every time you receive a promoted communication from Youth Connect, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving select or all future communications. Alternatively, you can always send an empty email to unsubscribe@youthconnectmag.com to be delisted from all of our databases.

**Log files:** Our website servers logs some data of yours that is standard for most websites. This data includes the internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse and measure trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Note that IP addresses do not contain any personally identifiable information. We may use a number of tracking utilities that will analyse user behavior and movement on our sites.

**Cookies:** A cookie is a small piece of information that is stored on your computer and contains information about you. There are two types of cookies – session ID cookies and persistent cookies. While session ID cookies expire (and are deleted) as soon as you close the website on your browser, persistent cookies are present for longer periods of time. Youth Connect may use cookies for its commenting, or contributor system. Youth Connect website may also uses cookies for the delivery of targeted ads. These cookies may not necessarily be controlled by Youth Connect but by our trusted Web advertising partners that includes, but is not limited to, Google.

### **Who else has access to my information?**

Information that is not personally identifiable will be accessible by our advertising-serving partners. This information includes no information that is personally identifiable.

We are also using feed aggregating service FeedBurner’s systems to help you send email subscriptions. Privacy policy of Feedburner can be found here <http://www.feedburner.com/fb/a/privacy>

You can find out privacy policy of Google, whose Analytics, Advertising, and other services for website we use, here – <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

### **Third Party Links**

Youth Connect and its sites may contain links to pieces of content that are not a part of Youth Connect or its sites. These outward links are the property of their respective owners and these may collect additional information of yours per their own respective privacy policy.

Users of Youth Connect and its sites are requested to use their own discretion before using or accessing these links.

### **Bottom Line**

Whenever you will provide us information, we will use it as discretely as possible. We will not share your personal information with third parties unless you give us consent to. Privacy is a personal matter and we recommend that you be careful and responsible while posting comments/ participating in contests/ contacting us for any matter.
